<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/directors.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>Director's List award</title>
		<description>An award given to students who obtain 3.5 or higher GPA in a semester and are members of MEP/MSP.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">The Dean's List Award</span>
<p align="left">This award is given to students who maintain a GPA of 3.5 or higher for a specific semester and are members of MESA Engineering Program (MEP) and/or Maximizing Science Potential (MSP).</p>
<p align="left">I received this award in fall 2011.</p>

<p align="left">To see the full size award click <a href="files/director.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p> ]]></content>
	</item>

	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/meps.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>MESA Participation Award</title>
		<description>An award given to students who have an outstanding participate in the MESA programs.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">MESA Participation Award</span>
<p align="left">I received this award for my outstanding participation in the MESA Engineering Program (MEP) and Maximizing Science Potential (MSP) programs.</p>
<p align="left">This award also includes a $500 stipend.</p>

<p align="left">To see the full size award click <a href="files/mep.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p> ]]></content>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/olympicss.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>MESA Olympics Award</title>
		<description>An award given to students who participate in the MESA Olympics & Robotics Competition.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">MESA Olympics & Robotics Competition Participation Award</span>
<p align="left">I received this award for my participation in the 19th MESA Olympics.</p>
<p align="left">The MESA Olympics is a test competition between groups of four. There are three levels of the test all in which cover chemistry, physics and calculus.</p>

<p align="left">To see the full size award click <a href="files/olympics.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p> ]]></content>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/deanss.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>Dean's List award</title>
		<description>An award given to students who obtain 3.5 or higher GPA in a semester.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">The Dean's List Award</span>
<p align="left">This award is given to students who maintain a GPA of 3.5 or higher for a specific semester.</p>
<p align="left">I received this award for the fall semester of 2011.</p>

<p align="left">To see the full size letter click <a href="files/deans.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p> ]]></content>
	</item>

	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/LSAMPs.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>LSAMP Participation Award</title>
		<description>An award given to students who participate in the LSAMP program.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">LSAMP Participation Award</span>
<p align="left">This award is given to students who participate in the LSAMP summer pathway through calculus.</p>

<p align="left">To see the full size award click <a href="files/LSAMP.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p> ]]></content>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/pulls.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>P.U.L.L. Recongnition award</title>
		<description>An award given  to students who volunteered in the PULL program.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title"><b>P</b>romoting <b>U</b>niversity <b>L</b>earning and <b>L</b>eadership Award</span>
<p align="left">This award is my first award at San Diego State University. This award was given to me for my participation at the PULL program as a mentor for a high school junior. For more information about the PULL program visit my volunteering section.</p>

<p align="left">To see the full size award click <a href="files/pull.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p> ]]></content>
	</item>

	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/brave.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>ECV Braves Recognition</title>
		<description>One of the hardest awards that a student can get at El Cajon Valley High School.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Braves Recognition Award</span>
<p align="left">This Award is only given at the end of the semester for one student who has an outstanding performance in a specific subject.</p>

<p align="left">I received this award for my performance at the Virtual Enterprise class in which I was the Vice President of Technology for the company. I did not only fulfill my responsibilities, but also took upon becoming the technician, tech support, website designer, graphics design and many other roles that our team was missing.</span></p>

<p align="left">To see the full size award click <a href="files/Brave.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p> ]]></content>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/ROP.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>ROP Business and Computers</title>
		<description>One of the best business training programs in San Diego.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">ROP Business and Computers</span>
<p align="left">ROP is a training program in which trains students to be successfull in business. Business and Computers class provided the training need to use computers in any form of business.</p>

<p align="left">To see the full size award click <a href="files/ROPs.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<p align="left">To see the full detailed version of this award click <a href="files/ROP.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p> ]]></content>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/coms.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>ROP Business and Computers Appreciation</title>
		<description>A certificate given instead of the Braves recongnition award.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Certificate of Appreciation</span>
<p align="left">Given for me for my outstanding performance in ROP Business and Computers instead of the Braves Recognition Award because of the school rules about the braves recongnition award. A student can only be nominated once for the braves awrad in the same department.</p>

<p align="left">To see the full size award click <a href="files/com.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>]]></content>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/PIQEs.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>PIQE recongnition award</title>
		<description>A certificate given to student who participated in the PIQE.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title"><b>P</b>arent <b>I</b>nstitute for <b>Q</b>uality <b>E</b>ducation</span>
<p align="left">An award given for my participation and volunteering at the PIQE weekly meetings. For more information about the PIQE check out the volunteering section.</p>

<p align="left">To see the full size award click <a href="files/PIQE.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>]]></content>
	</item>
		
	<item>
		<thumbnail>images/JAs.jpg</thumbnail>
		<title>Junior Achievement</title>
		<description>A certificate given to student who completed the JA training program.</description>
		
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title"><b>J</b>unior <b>A</b>chievement</span>
<p align="left">An award given for my participation and completing the JA training program. For more information about the JA program visit their official <a href="http://www.jasandiego.org" target="_new">website</a>.</p>

<p align="left">To see the full size award click <a href="files/JA.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>]]></content>
	</item>
</items>